♪ ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've been incredibly patient.
For the last two weeks you've
heard witness after witness
say the same thing...
that Dave Travis,
world championship
tennis player,
is a man of violent
temper, that he is angry
and that he is unpredictable,
both on the court
and off the court.
That Dave Travis is
volatile, a poor loser
and holds grudges.
And, ladies and gentlemen,
that Dave Travis killed his
archrival Victor Tomassio.
Victor Tomassio was also
a top-ranked tennis player
and Dave Travis was
determined to beat him
at the Tournament of
Champions here in Atlanta.
Advantage Tomassio.
Out.
Game, set, match Tomassio.
5-7, 6-4, 7-6, 5-7, 6-2.
Dave Travis lost
to his archrival.
And once again, he was furious.
But he wasn't furious just
because he lost the match.
No, he was furious because
he considered Victor Tomassio
a rival off the court as well.
Hold on, Tomassio,
we're not finished.
Save it for next time, Travis.
Hey, come on, you guys.
You stay away from my wife.
Travis, you're crazy!
You hit on her every chance
you get, you lousy creep.
Hey, come on, come on.
Hey, you come near Debbie
again and you're dead.
A dozen people heard Mr. Travis
threaten the decedent that day.
Among them, Gil McDevitt,
Peter Southcott,
Sarah McClain.
All professional tennis players.
All of them have toured
with Mr. Travis for years.
And all of them have testified
that Dave Travis
hated Victor Tomassio.
And there was the testimony
of the security guard
Martin Polowsky.
Please remember,
the only other person
the security guard saw
enter the room that day
was Carl Spivak... Hey, Victor.
Mr. Tomassio's coach. Come on.
Let's go.
You and Sarah got a match.
What's the deal, you...?
Motive and opportunity...
Dave Travis had both.
And the murder
weapon, this weight...
You've all heard
how it was found
in the back of Dave Travis' car.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what more do we need?
Again, I thank you
for your patience,
and I ask you to
do one more thing.
Serve justice.
Find the defendant guilty.
Thank you.
Mr. Matlock.
Uh, ladies and gentlemen,
you have heard from
the district attorney
that Dave Travis was angry,
that he doesn't like losing.
Well, I'm with him on that.
I don't like to lose either.
How about you?
And-and that, and
that Dave Travis
took a punch at a man
that made a pass at his wife.
Made a pass at his wife.
Well, I'm not sure that I
wouldn't do the same thing.
How about you?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Yeah.
As to the day that, uh,
Victor Tomassio died,
the district attorney
has said that Dave Travis
bludgeoned him to death
with his hand weight.
Did anybody see it?
No.
Someone did see Dave Travis
go in Victor's dressing room,
but what went on in there?
The district attorney
doesn't know.
She wasn't there.
She can only suggest.
Well, I can do that, too.
And what I suggest
happened in there that day
is something entirely different.
Dave Travis challenged
Victor Tomassio,
promised to beat him
on the tennis court,
and left him very much alive.
As to the alleged evidence...
Anyone could have put that
weight in Dave Travis' car.
Anyone.
This entire case is built
on circumstantial
evidence so flimsy
it cries out for a
verdict of not guilty.
I know that maybe some of you
have formed a personal opinion
of Dave Travis based on
his professional reputation.
I suppose that's human nature.
But justice calls for facts.
We're here to serve justice.
And to do that,
we must render a verdict...
of innocent.
Thank you.
Honey, everything's
going to be all right, okay?
Yeah, yeah, all
right, we'll see.
Okay. Thanks.
The jury was only
out four hours.
Is that good or bad?
Oh, it's hard to tell.
I have a feeling it all boils
down to how much they like you,
and whether they believe you.
Look at them.
A bunch of losers.
All together they won't
make as much in their lifetime
as I made in the
last couple months.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
The defendant will please rise.
We find the
defendant, David Travis,
guilty of first degree murder.
That jury stinks!
The system stinks!
You stink, too!
I'm innocent, damn it!
What the hell
happened in there, huh?
They didn't like you.
What's that got to
do with anything?
I kept trying to tell you,
people who sit on a
jury are just people.
And in cases like this
where the evidence is
largely circumstantial,
they tend to go by
their gut feelings.
And their gut feeling
was that you killed
Victor Tomassio.
What do you want me to do,
walk into court every
day and kiss a baby?
So nobody likes me.
I don't give a damn.
I didn't kill Victor Tomassio.
Well, I...
Well, why didn't you prove it?
Well, I'm sorry.
I-I really am sorry.
I feel terrible about it.
Good. Good, and you're
going to feel a lot worse.
I told my wife to stop
payment on your check.
Guard.
Michelle.
In here.
Michelle!
What?
We've got to find a way
to get this case retried.
Okay.
Any ideas how?
No.
But-But now that
Dave's been convicted,
maybe whoever
killed Victor will relax
and we can find whatever
we missed the first time.
All the suspects
we've investigated...
Sarah McClain, Peter
Southcott and Gil McDevitt...
Will be playing in a tournament
in Los Angeles next week.
Oh, I've got that
Jefferson case.
I'll get a continuance.
You've had three.
I'm not involved in
the Jefferson case.
I'll go to L.A.
Okay.
And I can take Conrad
off the Jefferson case.
And he wasn't involved
with Dave Travis;
maybe he'll have a fresh eye.
Sure.
Yeah.
I really appreciate
this, Michelle.
Yeah.
You know, Dave
Travis isn't easy.
He isn't nice.
He's a real jackass.
But he's right about one thing.
I hate losing.
Losing stinks.
Did you know he stopped
payment on my check?
Jerk.
Jackass.
Well, Gil McDevitt
is already here.
Sarah McClain
and Peter Southcott
are due to arrive later.
Any one suspect hot?
Not yet.
Michelle, this guy, Dave
Travis, has a mean temper.
And he did threaten to
kill... What's his name?
Victor Tomassio. Yes.
You think Ben could be wrong?
Sure, it's possible.
Sure is.
I hope not though, don't you?
Yeah.
You see how he got me
out here without packing?
No way.
You mean... Yes.
What you see is what I got.
No!
Stop.
No, you look nice.
Right, right.
You just stick around
me a few days, you'll see.
Stop!
And... cut.
Looks like we, uh,
just found Gil McDevitt.
Okay, everybody, that's a wrap.
Please, no.
Stay back behind
the gate, please.
Come on. He's not
coming out. Ladies, please.
If you don't stay back, you're
gonna all have to leave. Go...
Please!
Unlocked. You can
go ahead and take it.
Hello again, Mr. McDevitt.
Michelle Thomas.
What are you doing here?
Let's just say we're
not totally satisfied
with the jury verdict.
You shooting a movie?
It's a commercial.
Oh.
Oh, you represent Avir Wear now?
Exclusively.
Ah.
Yeah, I had a pair of
Avir tennis shoes once.
Never fit right.
Of course, that was
back when they were
endorsed exclusively
by Victor Tomassio.
Like I told you before,
I was in hydrotherapy
at the time of the murder.
Alone in hydrotherapy?
You see these
teenage girls over there?
They follow me everywhere.
When I'm in hydrotherapy,
they're outside the door.
And if you think I could've
sneaked out, killed Victor
and sneaked back in
without being swarmed
by these crazed teeny
boppers, well, forget it.
How much did you say
Avir Sportswear pays you?
It's been in the papers.
One million very big ones.
You know, for
that kind of money,
smart guy like
you could figure out
how to elude a
few teenage girls.
Good luck with the
tournament, Mr. McDevitt.
Hey, brought you some books.
I don't want to read!
Dave, you're not dead yet.
We found out
that... Gil McDevitt
approached Avir Sportswear
before Victor
Tomassio was killed.
Now, is there any reason why
this Gil needed a lot of money?
I don't know.
Now, I know
you're feeling kind of low.
Work on it.
Who is Louis Castille?
The guy calls himself a coach.
But he's a joke.
Why? What's he got
to do with this case?
He's Gil's new coach.
Gil fired Carl Spivak?
Right after the trial.
Think it'd have anything
to do with Victor's murder?
No. No, no, none.
You know why this happened, Ben?
The jury made a mistake.
No, no, no.
They couldn't wait
to make this mistake.
You know why?
Because they hate me.
That's right. That's right.
Everybody hates me.
I'm too good.
I'm too talented.
I mean, they're like,
they're like vultures.
You know, they can't
wait to bring you down.
You made them mad at you.
Don't do that next time.
And you have some friends.
Hell, I'm your friend.
You're the man I
paid $100,000 to,
and you got me
convicted of murder.
Would a friend do that?
You stopped payment
on the check, remember?
But that's okay; I like
to earn my money.
And we'll figure this thing out.
I hate losing worse than you do.
Well, look at that.
Read your books.
And talk to, talk
to the chaplain.
Yeah, talk to the chaplain.
Chaplains like everybody.
Hi.
Sarah, hi.
It's all right.
Hello, good morning.
Hi.
Uh, Sarah? Hey, could I
just get your autograph?
Hi, I'm Michelle Thomas.
I know who you are.
I'd like to talk to you.
Could I ask you a
couple of questions?
The trial's over.
Thank you so much.
Well, uh, maybe later?
Excuse me. Forget it. Sir?
Bye.
You're terrific!
Yeah, they should
be back in a minute.
Hey, Johnny, how you doing?
You said that to Ilie Nastase?
And lived to talk about it.
See, now I got to believe
coaching somebody
like Gil McDevitt, that's
got to keep you busy.
Suddenly, everybody
wants me to be their coach.
But going to the bank,
that's what keeps me busy.
See you, pal.
Enjoy your trip.
Thought you were gonna
buy some new clothes.
Yeah, I did.
What do you think, huh?
Oh.
Went to one of those
Laundromat places. Uh-huh.
They got this little room.
I went in. Yeah?
Read a couple of magazines.
Yeah, you're as good as new.
Thank you.
You were talking
to Louis Castille?
Yeah.
I don't know what it takes
to coach tennis, but I know
that windbag does not have it.
Mm, Peter Southcott.
Yeah, he and Victor
were doubles partners.
He hated Victor.
Remind me.
Well, Peter Southcott's
original partner
was his brother Philip.
Only, Philip was killed
in an automobile accident
after the French Open in '84.
Victor Tomassio
was at the wheel.
He wasn't charged with anything,
but Southcott never forgave him.
Why were they doubles partners?
They were good together.
And doubles is all Peter
Southcott can play anymore.
Oh, oh, Ben called. He
wants us to look into a house
that Gil McDevitt just
bought here in L.A.
Don't tennis players
have houses all over?
Yeah.
Not houses worth over a million
deeded to someone else.
Okay, everything's
fine in the bedroom.
Down here in the living room...
Hello. I want you
to put the big couch
right over there with a
chair on either side of it.
Hi.
Hello, hi.
I'm Michelle Thomas.
I'm an attorney.
Oh, what a cutie.
Hi.
How old? Six months.
Oh.
Alexander Timothy Matthews.
Hello, Alexander
Timothy Matthews.
I'm Leslie Matthews. Hi.
Is something wrong
with the paperwork?
Oh, no.
As far as I know,
everything's fine.
Good.
You own this house
and everything in it,
lock, stock and barrel.
It's a dream come true.
It's not every day
someone's just
handed the deed
to a house in Bel Air,
that's for sure.
Gil is one generous young man.
Is he a relative of yours?
Who'd you say you were again?
Michelle Thomas.
Gil and I have had
dealings recently.
You think you'll be
seeing him today?
I might.
Would you tell him I stopped by?
Sure.
Boy, you came a long way.
Everything make it in one piece?
We made it.
That's all that matters.
Hmm.
What are you doing here?
Ah, heard you
bought a new house.
Thought I'd drop by and
see how the other half live.
Yeah, I bought this house
for my cousin Leslie here.
Oh. Your cousin.
Yeah, we're very close.
She just went
through a ugly divorce.
Husband left her and
the baby without a cent.
So you bought them
a new house and furnished it
and flew them all the
way out here from, uh...?
Um, New York.
Well, the labels on these boxes
say they were
shipped from Chicago.
Why don't you just leave?
All right.
But you must know that I am
gonna check into all this.
I met Leslie in a bar,
little over a year ago.
And I, uh, spent
the night with her.
Just one night.
Six months later, I
get this call from her
that she's-she's
pregnant with my kid.
Says she's gonna go to
the papers with the story,
and the blood test to prove it,
if-if I don't give
her what she wants.
A one-way ticket out of Chicago
and a furnished home in L.A.
Listen, if people found
out I had an illegitimate son,
I could be out millions.
I mean, I had to
go along with her.
Expensive.
Is that why you started
hustling a contract with Avir?
I was just putting out feelers.
I had nothing to do with
what happened to Victor.
Ask Leslie!
She was right there.
Hell, for that matter, you
might as well ask Louis Castille.
What's he got to do with it?
Okay, the afternoon
of the murder,
I was sitting in
hydrotherapy, like I said,
except I wasn't alone.
Leslie showed up.
Said that she needed some cash.
Just enough to get by
until the move to California.
So I give her everything
I got, and she leaves.
Only, turns out, Louis
Castille is in the next room
this whole time and
overhears everything.
So he starts making threats.
Told you to, uh, fire
Carl Spivak and hire him
or he'd go to the press.
Listen, I know I
lied in this trial,
but there's no reason this
has to go public, is there?
Do you mean, even though you
fathered a child out of wedlock,
committed perjury,
obstructed justice
and gave into blackmail,
since you're not a murderer,
everything's okay, right?
Yeah, right.
Advantage Southcott.
Game, set and match,
Southcott-MacArthur.
6-3, 2-6 and 7-5.
Congratulations.
Nice match. Ah...
Thank you.
Michelle Thomas.
I'm an attorney.
We met briefly during
Dave Travis' trial.
Right.
So after playing doubles
with Victor Tomassio
for almost a decade,
what's it like being partnered
with someone else?
It's different,
it's very different.
But, um, Victor's dead; I'll
just have to get used to it.
Are you saying
that Victor's death
is the reason you
have a new partner?
Of course.
Well, why were the
tournament officials informed
that you were playing
with, um, Ted MacArthur
and not Victor Tomassio
before Tomassio was killed?
All right, so Victor dumped me.
So what?
So why did you lie about it?
Victor said I was
losing my game.
You want me to go shout
that from the rooftops?
Excuse me.
Must have made you pretty mad.
Especially considering what
happened to your brother.
I know you blame
Victor for his death.
But Victor was your meal ticket.
Playing doubles with him was the
only way you could make a living.
But when he dumped you,
all that changed, didn't it?
You're way off base, lady.
Where did you say you were
at the time of the murder?
Ask my lawyer.
Ms. McClain?
Yeah, that's me.
I'm all tied up in knots.
Especially my neck.
You are from Dr. Morgan's
office, aren't you?
Tension... yeah,
we'll get right on that.
Take care of that right now.
Harder.
I'm not made out of glass.
Okay.
Hey, I hear you
won your first match.
Nice going.
Piece of cake.
The real competition
starts day after tomorrow.
Yeah, see, that's what I figure.
You're playing Ingrid
Jorgensen right?
Oh, you follow tennis?
Oh, my goodness,
are you kidding me?
You people are my life.
Victor Tomassio was my
main man, before he died.
Cat had a forehand
like an MX missile.
I miss watching him play.
Can I ask you something? See...
I heard that you and,
you know, you and Victor
were pretty good friends.
Yeah? Where'd you hear that?
I'm a masseur.
I mean, I was talking to Louis.
Castille?
Yeah. Can he talk?
Yeah, it's what he does best.
He was saying that you
and Victor were an item.
We dated.
When I discovered
what a jerk Victor was,
I stopped seeing him.
Whoo-hoo.
So you were pretty upset
when he broke it off, huh?
Hey, I told you, I broke it off.
It was a relief.
But you went on playing
mixed doubles with him.
Look, your job is to
relax me, all right?
And you're not doing it.
So either massage with
your mouth shut, or get out.
Okay.
Your cervical lumbar is now
aligned with your vertical hole.
How'd it go?
She had a relationship with
Victor Tomassio, all right,
and it did not have
a happy ending.
When I talked to
her before the trial,
she said she was in the
women's dressing room
at the time of the
murder... Alone, of course.
Hey, do you think
she's strong enough
to fracture a person's
skull with a hand weight?
Oh, yeah.
There's no doubt about that.
Let's call Ben.
Look, I want to get
something straight here.
You're right, I hated Victor.
And yeah, I even
thought about killing him...
I daydreamed about
it... But I didn't do it.
Can you prove that?
I was in the steam room.
Look, don't you think
if I'd have killed him
I'd have come up with
a better story than that?
Not necessarily.
Not if you could
frame Dave Travis.
No, uh-uh.
Dave and I were friends.
Look-Look, we roomed
together on the tour
before he ever married Debbie.
We were buddies. Ask him.
Ask anybody.
I could have killed Victor and
never given it a second thought,
but I could have never
done that to David.
Never.
♪ Chinatown, my Chinatown ♪
♪ When the lights are low... ♪
Eat-eat bean sprouts
with the lobster.
It's delicious.
♪ Dee-dee-dee, dee-dee-dee ♪
♪ Dee-dee, to and fro... ♪
Did you sleep last night?
Some. Off and on.
Huh. Well, that's
better than nothing.
Of course, sometimes
when you sleep like that,
you feel like you haven't
slept at all, don't you?
Yeah, right.
♪ Dee-dee-dee-dee, ump-pah-pah ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da... ♪
Hold it.
Why'd you bring this
Chinese food in here?
Oh, I know about jailhouse food,
and I heard you like Chinese.
Eat-eat some rice with the pork.
I-I read... I read a
piece on a Chinese fella,
lived to be 117.
Said it was because he
ate rice three times a day.
Well, why aren't you
having any, then?
I had Chinese last night.
So I thought I'd
settle for a hot dog.
Trying to hold on to my figure.
♪ Dee-dee-dee... ♪
You think Peter Southcott
would, uh, frame you for murder?
No.
No, no, he liked me.
He did?
Were you nice to him?
Not especially, no.
But he liked you?
Huh, that's good.
♪ Dee-dee-dee-dee... ♪
What about Sarah McClain?
Would Sarah kill a
man for jilting her?
She played to win.
Oh?
Conrad and Michelle
think it's Sarah.
Dee-dee-dee-da, Chinatown ♪
♪ Dee-dee... ♪
Hold it a second.
Why did you bring
this ukulele in here?
Oh, oh, I stopped
by Ray Templin's bar.
Ray plays piano.
We're trying to start a group.
I thought it would,
you know, pick you up.
Make you feel better.
Well, it's not making
me feel better, all right?
That's a shame.
Makes me feel better.
Dee-dee-dee-dee ♪
♪ Dee-dee-dee ♪
I'm gonna rot in here, you
know that? ♪ Da-da-da... ♪
Maybe not.
♪ Dee... ♪
You know...
Maybe Sarah could have done it.
I believe I'll go down
to the television station
and look at those
tapes on her again.
I'm gonna rot in here.
Well, you won't rot today.
You just had a big Chinese meal.
Eat the rest of that rice.
♪ Da-da-dom, ba-ra-ta-ta ♪
♪ When the lights are low... ♪
You the guy who was in here
last month watching this stuff?
Yeah.
So you already know who won.
I'm looking for something else.
Uh, can you find the
mixed doubles match
that Sarah McClain
and Victor Tomassio
were supposed to
play later that day?
Here we go. Yeah.
Can-Can you
freeze it right there?
C-Can you do
that? Stop it? Yeah.
Well, I'll be. That's it.
That's it. That's it. See?
I knew it.
I just knew it. See there?
That's it. That's it.
Hello.
What time's checkout?
Ben?
Did I wake you up?
It's 5:30 out here.
Is that right?
What time is checkout?
Um, noon.
Well, you and Conrad
come on home. You're done.
W-Why? What's going on?
You're right.
Sarah McClain
did it. I just know it.
Well, do you have enough
to move for a new trial?
Yeah.
But I need a hearing.
And for the hearing, I need her.
Oh, I'll just subpoena her.
Oh, no, I can't subpoena
her while she's out of state.
You'll have to
figure out something.
$50,000?!
Herb, you're not going to
actually pay her $50,000.
You just dangle
it in front of her
like a carrot on a stick.
Ben, I'm the president of
Boldaun Business Machines.
I have stockholders to answer
to, to say nothing of the SEC.
Herb, if you don't
help me out on this,
then this woman, guilty
of first degree murder,
is going to get off scot-free,
while an innocent man spends
the rest of his life in prison.
Is that fair?
But I sure as hell don't
want to give away $50,000.
You're not going to.
Just call Sarah McClain's agent.
Tell him you'll pay her $50,000
to come to your convention
down here in Atlanta,
and give your top
salesperson a tennis lesson.
What if her agent
insists on a contract?
Send him one. Send him 20.
She'll never render services.
Therefore, you'll never have
to pay him or her a red cent.
Swear?
Cross my heart.
Oh, I don't know, Ben.
Course, if you were
to sign something
that said, uh, you'd, uh,
make good any and all losses
Boldaun Business Machines
should somehow incur
because of this little
scheme of yours,
uh, then, uh...
A deal.
You're good for
the whole $50,000?
Okay.
Hello.
Hi. How you doing?
Did you hear the news?
Yep, two sets: 6-4, 6-2.
Thanks.
Oh, no, Neil...
No, I don't think so
'cause I only have four days
for the Denver
tournament, and I...
Fi... $50,000 for one day?!
Uh... where do I go?
The white zone is for
the immediate loading and
unloading of passengers only.
Miss-Miss McClain.
No parking.
Did you enjoy the
flight as much as I did?
Yeah, the flight was fine.
Are-Are you with the
Boldaun Corporation?
Masters?
Yes. No, excuse me.
Subpoena...
Damn.
Your Honor, this is a
defense motion for a new trial.
Your Honor, Mr. Matlock
had his chance
to present his case
at the time of trial.
If every attorney who was
dissatisfied with the verdict
did what he's doing, we'd
be here 24 hours a day.
Uh, Your Honor, we have
significant, newly
discovered evidence
not available to us
at the time of trial.
If this evidence had been
uncovered and presented
to the jury, a far different
verdict would have resulted.
Proceed, Mr. Matlock.
Thank you.
Uh, defense calls Miss
Sarah McClain to the stand.
The first thing I want to do is
apologize for any inconvenience
this hearing has caused you.
I-I understand that you
had to cancel an appearance
at the Boldaun Corporate
Convention here in Atlanta
in order to comply
with this subpoena.
That's all right.
Well, your misfortune
is our good fortune.
Uh, had you not
returned to Fulton County,
we'd never have been
able to subpoena you,
and you'd have been out of
the jurisdiction of this court.
Amazing.
It is... it is a
coincidence. It is, it is.
Now, uh, even though
this is, uh, just a hearing,
you are under oath.
You understand that,
do you, Miss McClain?
Yes.
Now... it has come
to my attention
th-that you and Victor Tomassio
were lovers, is that right?
Yes. Were you
lovers at the time
he was murdered?
No. Um, we had broken it
off about a month earlier.
"We'd..." Wait-wait
a minute. Wait.
You mean, he'd
broken it off, don't you?
No, actually, it was
a fairly mutual thing.
Oh, it was, huh?
Well, who are
Wade Willis and Sandy Roland?
They're my personal assistants.
They know you well?
Yes.
Didn't you tell them that
Victor broke up with you?
All right, Victor
broke up with me.
And that you were
very upset about it?
Yes.
You lied just now.
No, I didn't lie. I-I forgot.
Come on.
Our relationship was over with.
I-I put it behind me,
and I went on with my life.
And I forgot Victor.
I don't think so.
I think you were furious
with him breaking it off
and humiliating you like that.
He did humiliate you.
And I don't think
you could handle it.
And you didn't forget it, and so
you killed Victor
Tomassio, didn't you?
No, that's not true.
Your Honor,
Mr. Matlock has not produced
one shred of evidence
newly discovered or otherwise.
Mr. Matlock?
Right here, Your Honor,
if the court permits.
Go ahead, Mr. Matlock.
Thank you. Conrad?
Uh, just bring it... over here.
Well, hello, Doctor.
I haven't seen you in
a month of Sundays.
How's the family?
Mr. Matlock.
Sir?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I forgot where I was.
I guess the mind is
the second thing to go.
Mr. Matlock!
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Big Red.
Uh, I'm gonna show you
a couple of videotapes.
Now don't worry.
This won't hurt you.
This is a device we use often.
Now I want to show
you this first one,
and you tell me who
these people are playing.
That's me and
that's Eva Randolph.
Looks like the finals for
the Atlanta tournament.
That's right, and you won, okay?
Now tell-tell-tell us what-what
this is here in just a moment.
What's that?
The start of the final
match for mixed doubles
at the same tournament.
That's right.
And that's a match
that was never played,
because at the very
moment that you were walking
onto the court, Victor's
coach was walking into
his players' dressing
room where he found
him murdered.
Were you in Victor's
dressing room that day?
No.
At no time after you
finished your singles match
between this and when
you walked on the court
for the doubles match,
you didn't visit
Victor's dressing room?
No.
Then... how did you get this?
That's an Avir wristband.
See, here in your singles,
you're not wearing
an Avir wristband.
In fact, there's nothing
on your left wrist at all,
but here there is.
Where'd you get that?
When I changed clothes
for the mixed doubles match,
I discovered that I was
out of clean wristbands,
so I used one of Victor's.
Oh.
Oh...
So...
you did
go to Victor's
dressing room that day.
Oh, no, he gave
me that wristband
while we were still dating.
Oh, no. No, no,
that's impossible.
That's impossible.
See, Avir has a new
logo on the wristband.
You see there?
Mm-hmm. It's so new
it's not even in the stores yet.
And the company didn't supply
Victor with these wristbands
until the Atlanta
tournament had begun.
And he was the only one
permitted to wear them.
Now let's run
through that again.
Were you or were you not
in Victor's dressing
room that day?
Yes, uh... now I remember.
Um, I needed a wristband,
so I used one of Victor's.
It's no big deal. I forgot.
You just lied again.
You were in Victor's
room that day.
And did you plan it,
or did it just happen,
that in your anger you picked
up one of his hand weights
and hit him in the
head with it? No!
And Victor, in trying
to protect himself,
burned you with the
cigarette he was smoking
on your left wrist?
No, that's not true.
You know, I almost forgot that.
I-I almost overlooked it
because it seemed so odd
for a fine athlete like
Victor Tomassio to smoke,
but he did.
And while you were killing
him with that hand weight,
he was grinding that
cigarette into your wrist.
No, he wasn't. And when you were
done killing him, you
wiped your fingerprints
off the hand weight,
covered it with a towel
till you could put it
in Dave Travis' car,
and then you put on
one of Victor's wristbands
to cover the burn.
I did not.
Yes, you did.
Trouble was, once you
put on that wristband,
you couldn't take it
off because if you did,
all that burned skin
would come off with it.
But when you were
alone, you did take it off.
And that's what happened.
It must have hurt like hell.
That burned skin
coming... rrrkh...
And all it left was a kind
of a... big, round, red hole.
There's nothing
wrong with my wrist.
Perfect.
You remember that man
I spoke to a while ago?
I thought I saw a little
look of recognition.
Dr. Steinbeck
does beautiful work,
doesn't he?
You want to tell the judge
who Dr. Steinbeck is?
When you realized that that
big red burn was gonna turn
into a big scar...
you went to see Dr. Steinbeck,
one of the finest plastic
surgeons in the country.
And he fixed it up for you.
Now... you want to tell the
judge what Dr. Steinbeck did,
or... do you want the
good doctor to do it himself?
I'd just as soon not
answer any more questions
until I talk with my lawyer.
Oh! So...
So, uh, now what?
Well, I've been
offered a cool million
to write my memoirs.
I'm gonna name
names, ruin reputations.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah. You know, like they say,
"Don't get mad, get even."
Yeah.
Come on, honey.
We got a lot of
celebrating to do.
Thank you, Mr. Matlock.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you all.
Uh-huh.
Back to his old self.
Arrogant.
Yeah.
Did you get your check?
Oh, yes.
Dinner.
Yeah, okay.
Great, great. Yes.
Okay, I'll go home and
change. What about you?
Fast as I can. I'm
sick of these clothes.
You need some new wardrobe?
Oh, yeah.
Tomorrow morning
we'll-we'll stop by
and see my tailor.
Ah...
www.tvsubtitles.net